[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2016-08-07 20:16:33
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:856
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,楷体,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.73,0:00:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.67,0:00:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近老是玩手机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交女朋友了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.00,0:00:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.00,0:00:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必隐藏的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.51,0:00:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧！   真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.19,0:00:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆也长大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.28,0:00:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么样的女孩呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.17,0:00:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.00,0:00:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一个班的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.41,0:00:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很普通
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.33,0:00:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么样的孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.06,0:00:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈很在意哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.23,0:00:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次带来家里玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.00,0:01:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.08,0:01:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.63,0:01:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈很欢迎小隆的女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.09,0:01:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.19,0:01:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有机会我会带回来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.61,0:01:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸听到这个也会高兴的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.78,0:01:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要告诉爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.05,0:01:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.34,0:01:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  这是小隆和妈妈的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.70,0:01:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公暂时在外地工作  我和儿子两人生活
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.25,0:01:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子在我眼里一直是小孩  他现在也长大了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.00,0:01:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为妈妈 儿子有了女朋友 我应该高兴才对
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.32,0:01:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上觉得有点寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.59,0:02:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的房间是什么样的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.00,0:02:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一般的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.82,0:02:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么好看的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.70,0:02:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么说？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.38,0:02:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很想看的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.06,0:02:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好紧张啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.52,0:02:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈在吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.35,0:02:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果紧张的话可以回去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.75,0:02:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 都来到这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.14,0:02:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.35,0:02:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位就是小隆的女朋吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.92,0:02:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.00,0:02:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫栗原
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.17,0:02:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 真可爱的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.80,0:03:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和这么可爱的女孩交往 真不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.04,0:03:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.01,0:03:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.06,0:03:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么态度
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.22,0:03:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.81,0:03:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是小隆的房间吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.03,0:03:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很普通的房间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.86,0:03:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有色情书吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.43,0:03:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这边吗？  没有的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.55,0:03:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏在这里吧？  没有
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.47,0:03:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.11,0:03:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.54,0:03:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.29,0:04:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵喜欢小隆哪里呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.61,0:04:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 好啰嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.50,0:04:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.51,0:04:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.70,0:04:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿茶给他们才行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.60,0:05:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要乱翻来看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.20,0:05:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.38,0:05:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小隆的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.83,0:05:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是真心喜欢小隆的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.38,0:05:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以能交往我很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.07,0:05:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能在小隆的房间里我就很幸福了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.43,0:05:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.05,0:05:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.51,0:07:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.00,0:07:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.54,0:07:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.61,0:07:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是小隆你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.05,0:07:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.92,0:07:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.54,0:07:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很喜欢小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.53,0:08:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.24,0:08:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.47,0:09:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.80,0:09:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 我好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.22,0:09:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面也让我看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.75,0:09:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.28,0:09:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.25,0:09:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快让我看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.86,0:09:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.01,0:09:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒挺了 好痛哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.23,0:09:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.00,0:09:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱掉比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.73,0:10:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.78,0:11:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.95,0:11:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒这么大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.97,0:12:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.00,0:12:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆。。。小隆的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.21,0:12:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么让我这么兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.56,0:12:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 要出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.04,0:12:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么快吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.97,0:12:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前看了色情书
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.71,0:13:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用肉棒摩擦奶子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.39,0:13:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗？  可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.29,0:13:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.01,0:14:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 肉棒好硬哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.05,0:15:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.35,0:15:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要出来了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.76,0:15:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵也让我舔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.72,0:15:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要舔吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.85,0:15:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.31,0:16:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.08,0:16:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.00,0:16:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.77,0:17:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.06,0:17:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老公暂时在外地工作
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.86,0:17:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很久没见过男人的肉棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.07,0:17:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是儿子的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.84,0:17:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也让我有强烈的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.04,0:18:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子真漂亮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.04,0:18:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再带她来玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.72,0:18:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.34,0:18:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.10,0:18:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.95,0:18:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生病了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.26,0:18:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.71,0:18:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.65,0:19:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎没发烧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.07,0:19:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵的电话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.36,0:19:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 我吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.47,0:19:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子的肉棒比想象的大
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.62,0:20:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我很兴奋  不想把他让给女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.01,0:20:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.41,0:20:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越强烈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.90,0:21:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.36,0:21:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像和你做爱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.13,0:22:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.60,0:22:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子舔肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.45,0:22:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会射的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.12,0:23:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.87,0:23:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.80,0:23:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被妈妈看见的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.40,0:25:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.52,0:25:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.47,0:25:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.28,0:25:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前让小葵口交了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.77,0:25:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈看见了后
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.78,0:25:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子变得奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.59,0:25:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.04,0:26:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.42,0:26:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.18,0:26:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.07,0:26:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.28,0:26:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是母子
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.73,0:26:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈抑制不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.90,0:26:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.64,0:26:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子变得奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.02,0:26:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.01,0:26:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.57,0:26:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.27,0:27:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆  不行的 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.40,0:27:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.27,0:27:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.12,0:27:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.90,0:27:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.10,0:27:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.38,0:27:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.66,0:27:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.16,0:27:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.20,0:27:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.94,0:27:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.14,0:27:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.48,0:28:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看妈妈的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.36,0:28:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.33,0:28:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.51,0:28:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的身体很脏吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.62,0:28:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.87,0:28:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.30,0:28:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是母子 不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.38,0:29:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说不行 勃起得很厉害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.30,0:29:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.40,0:29:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.01,0:29:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.64,0:29:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得这么硬了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.63,0:30:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.44,0:30:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说不行 这么大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.16,0:30:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.51,0:30:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.73,0:30:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.54,0:30:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.44,0:30:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰到妈妈的骚穴了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.83,0:31:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.28,0:31:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.67,0:31:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得好硬呢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.07,0:31:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.09,0:31:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让妈妈看肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.45,0:31:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.12,0:31:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.31,0:31:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.88,0:31:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.25,0:31:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.59,0:32:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.62,0:32:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么硬呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.06,0:32:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好涨哦
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.02,0:32:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多一点 多摩擦一些
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.57,0:32:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.34,0:32:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好硬好爽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.75,0:32:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.04,0:32:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.59,0:33:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.32,0:33:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.52,0:33:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.08,0:33:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.83,0:33:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.03,0:33:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来摸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.64,0:33:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.97,0:33:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骚穴变得这么湿了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.06,0:33:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想要小隆的肉棒来插
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.39,0:33:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈变得这么湿了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.05,0:34:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.00,0:34:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听淫荡的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.44,0:34:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄出淫荡的声音吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.46,0:34:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.66,0:34:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.61,0:34:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动起来
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.07,0:34:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用手搅动妈妈的骚穴
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.00,0:34:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.04,0:34:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 很棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.04,0:34:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.77,0:34:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.54,0:34:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.23,0:35:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.66,0:35:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.43,0:35:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 更多
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.01,0:35:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入两个手指
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.48,0:35:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搅动起来
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.73,0:35:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴很爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.59,0:35:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用手指搅动吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.10,0:35:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.07,0:35:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.04,0:35:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.28,0:36:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.01,0:36:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.74,0:36:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入妈妈的骚穴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.32,0:36:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.11,0:36:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈好想要小隆的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.66,0:36:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子变得奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.52,0:36:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要小隆的肉棒插入
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.03,0:36:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.02,0:37:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.00,0:37:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.40,0:37:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说不行
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.05,0:37:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒变这么大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.40,0:37:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.97,0:37:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸了妈妈的骚穴 肉棒变得这么大了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.68,0:37:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得更硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.07,0:38:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.06,0:38:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.62,0:38:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.01,0:38:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被爸爸看到怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.99,0:38:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真啰嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.66,0:38:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在不想听到你爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.11,0:38:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只关心小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.47,0:39:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.52,0:39:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有小葵了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.02,0:39:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.87,0:39:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.47,0:39:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈可以让小隆更爽
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.06,0:39:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.62,0:39:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.53,0:39:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.61,0:40:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.63,0:41:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.81,0:41:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.40,0:41:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.43,0:41:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有小葵了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.37,0:41:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.55,0:41:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.87,0:41:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真啰嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.23,0:41:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈会让你闭嘴的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.26,0:41:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.47,0:42:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.13,0:42:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.01,0:42:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能舔
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.47,0:42:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:42:42.29,0:42:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.69,0:42:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.72,0:43:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈舔了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.53,0:43:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.93,0:43:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:43:43.80,0:43:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:43:46.91,0:43:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听妈妈的话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:43:50.06,0:43:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.42,0:43:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在说这种话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:44:01.53,0:44:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.25,0:44:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:44:07.94,0:44:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.44,0:44:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.35,0:44:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.02,0:44:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地看着插入的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.81,0:44:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.43,0:44:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.21,0:44:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直好想要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:42.48,0:44:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:44:46.04,0:44:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.00,0:44:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.64,0:44:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.53,0:44:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒插的好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:45:10.72,0:45:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:45:14.71,0:45:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:45:16.12,0:45:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.36,0:45:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比小葵更爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.57,0:45:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.75,0:45:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.46,0:45:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:45:39.26,0:45:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.67,0:45:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是家人
Dialogue: 0,0:45:46.03,0:45:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顶到深处了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.23,0:45:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴爽吗
Dialogue: 0,0:46:21.26,0:46:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地看妈妈的屁股哦
Dialogue: 0,0:46:43.81,0:46:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.10,0:46:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地看妈妈淫荡的屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:46:57.61,0:46:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以摸哦
Dialogue: 0,0:47:01.07,0:47:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:47:09.24,0:47:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.23,0:47:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:47:53.78,0:47:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:48:01.02,0:48:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.12,0:48:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不听话
Dialogue: 0,0:48:09.20,0:48:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要激烈做了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:22.07,0:48:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.32,0:48:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要嘴硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.52,0:48:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒这么硬了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:48:33.68,0:48:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴很爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:37.50,0:48:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诚实一点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:48.11,0:48:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴变得好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:55.64,0:48:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.35,0:49:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:49:26.02,0:49:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.11,0:49:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让妈妈高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:33.84,0:49:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:49:41.99,0:49:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆也让妈妈爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:49:47.68,0:49:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,0:49:49.60,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多动一些
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.01,0:50:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:50:01.68,0:50:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦 小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:50:17.14,0:50:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:50:21.94,0:50:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:46.05,0:50:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.01,0:50:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:50:51.29,0:50:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.07,0:50:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰动起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:56.34,0:50:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:51:10.38,0:51:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:51:12.60,0:51:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:51:15.54,0:51:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴
Dialogue: 0,0:51:18.03,0:51:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地感受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:25.12,0:51:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:51:27.22,0:51:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:51:41.35,0:51:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:51:43.53,0:51:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:48.21,0:51:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:51:53.11,0:51:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈会帮你的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:06.63,0:52:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:52:09.07,0:52:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力插吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:12.22,0:52:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:52:15.32,0:52:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把对小葵做的事都对妈妈做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:28.83,0:52:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让妈妈高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:35.64,0:52:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:52:46.54,0:52:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,0:52:48.41,0:52:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更快一些
Dialogue: 0,0:52:55.44,0:52:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插到花心了 好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:53:01.23,0:53:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:11.65,0:53:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.06,0:53:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多插一些
Dialogue: 0,0:53:28.77,0:53:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:53:34.72,0:53:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:53:36.48,0:53:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰动起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:42.55,0:53:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多动一些吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:47.12,0:53:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让妈妈的骚穴更爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:53.40,0:53:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰动起来
Dialogue: 0,0:54:59.52,0:54:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:54:00.99,0:54:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更爽一些吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.31,0:54:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:54:12.70,0:54:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对。。对。。更多
Dialogue: 0,0:54:15.04,0:54:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更用力一些
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.23,0:54:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:54:25.97,0:54:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.89,0:54:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 去了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:45.63,0:54:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:54:50.71,0:54:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴很爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:26.19,0:55:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力插妈妈的骚穴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:35.26,0:55:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:55:41.28,0:55:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:55:46.26,0:55:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比小葵更爽吧从
Dialogue: 0,0:55:51.74,0:55:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后也要继续和妈妈做
Dialogue: 0,0:56:12.94,0:56:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:56:15.05,0:56:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:56:22.03,0:56:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:56:53.69,0:56:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:57:20.01,0:57:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:22.15,0:57:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不行
Dialogue: 0,0:57:23.56,0:57:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不能射
Dialogue: 0,0:57:25.79,0:57:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:57:28.73,0:57:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:57:45.42,0:57:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:57:54.04,0:57:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:56.69,0:57:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多。。要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:18.24,0:58:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:58:20.02,0:58:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:58:22.29,0:58:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的 小隆
Dialogue: 0,0:58:25.07,0:58:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:58:32.25,0:58:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不毕忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:58:35.68,0:58:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射好多出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:58:47.23,0:58:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:17.97,0:59:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骚穴好湿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:26.81,0:59:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:30.55,0:59:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:31.17,0:59:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射好多出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:59:40.96,0:59:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:45.18,0:59:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 射了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:05.64,1:00:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:00:35.20,1:00:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:00:58.05,1:00:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,1:01:03.40,1:01:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:01:05.51,1:01:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,1:01:09.31,1:01:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈脑子坏掉了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:58.65,1:02:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上小心
Dialogue: 0,1:02:05.60,1:02:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,1:03:11.65,1:03:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明知道这样子不对 可我的骚穴被摸的感觉还残留着
Dialogue: 0,1:03:19.30,1:03:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后冲动得不得了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:41.66,1:03:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个。。。干嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:03:50.58,1:03:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,1:04:49.22,1:04:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:04:54.22,1:04:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:04:57.05,1:04:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,1:05:00.46,1:05:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮你搓背吧
Dialogue: 0,1:05:09.84,1:05:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,1:05:40.89,1:05:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:05:42.58,1:05:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,1:05:45.02,1:05:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,1:05:47.15,1:05:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮你洗身体
Dialogue: 0,1:06:06.36,1:06:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:06:07.89,1:06:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以  有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,1:06:11.08,1:06:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮你洗身体而已哦
Dialogue: 0,1:06:15.14,1:06:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实一点吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:25.55,1:06:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前经常一起洗的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:35.64,1:06:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:06:37.98,1:06:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要弄奶头
Dialogue: 0,1:06:40.59,1:06:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有弄
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.81,1:06:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗身体而已
Dialogue: 0,1:06:50.67,1:06:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以的
Dialogue: 0,1:06:55.31,1:06:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要洗干净才行的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:07:00.00,1:07:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是小孩了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:02.46,1:07:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久没有一起洗了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:08.03,1:07:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈会帮你洗干净的
Dialogue: 0,1:07:21.52,1:07:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:07:23.96,1:07:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不行
Dialogue: 0,1:07:28.05,1:07:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:07:52.76,1:07:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:07:56.44,1:08:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是洗身体而已哦
Dialogue: 0,1:08:08.03,1:08:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以的
Dialogue: 0,1:08:13.21,1:08:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,1:08:14.59,1:08:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,1:08:21.39,1:08:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:08:44.71,1:08:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:08:46.84,1:08:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时有好好洗吗
Dialogue: 0,1:08:53.06,1:08:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有洗的
Dialogue: 0,1:08:55.29,1:08:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,1:08:57.79,1:09:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很脏呢
Dialogue: 0,1:09:05.21,1:09:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:09:07.20,1:09:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好地洗
Dialogue: 0,1:09:10.31,1:09:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脚放这边吧
Dialogue: 0,1:09:13.77,1:09:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,1:09:35.07,1:09:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:09:48.80,1:09:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好洗干净哦
Dialogue: 0,1:10:07.45,1:10:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈帮你洗干净
Dialogue: 0,1:10:54.59,1:10:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:11:01.68,1:11:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里想要洗呢
Dialogue: 0,1:11:10.71,1:11:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:11:13.41,1:11:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:11:21.04,1:11:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:11:42.81,1:11:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:12:04.69,1:12:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:12:07.67,1:12:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮妈妈洗身体吧
Dialogue: 0,1:12:42.09,1:12:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的身体
Dialogue: 0,1:12:44.61,1:12:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,1:12:46.56,1:12:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,1:12:48.62,1:12:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多摸一些
Dialogue: 0,1:13:04.16,1:13:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:13:07.70,1:13:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把女朋友甩了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:13.07,1:13:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起小葵 妈妈的身体更漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:22.39,1:13:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:13:25.42,1:13:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:13:27.49,1:13:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是母子
Dialogue: 0,1:13:29.74,1:13:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以的
Dialogue: 0,1:13:32.74,1:13:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:34.62,1:13:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈这么喜欢小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:13:40.00,1:13:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:13:47.46,1:13:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:13:50.25,1:13:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:53.02,1:13:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:55.58,1:13:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢 和我接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:59.61,1:14:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,1:14:02.56,1:14:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:14:06.25,1:14:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我接吻
Dialogue: 0,1:14:38.63,1:14:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:14:47.09,1:14:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:14:49.48,1:14:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸出舌头
Dialogue: 0,1:14:53.85,1:14:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌头
Dialogue: 0,1:14:57.40,1:14:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,1:14:59.37,1:15:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更长一些
Dialogue: 0,1:15:01.55,1:15:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸出来
Dialogue: 0,1:15:03.09,1:15:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,1:15:05.50,1:15:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,1:15:44.84,1:15:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:15:47.53,1:15:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢妈妈吗
Dialogue: 0,1:15:56.34,1:15:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不讨厌
Dialogue: 0,1:16:01.68,1:16:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢吗
Dialogue: 0,1:16:04.32,1:16:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜欢吗
Dialogue: 0,1:16:08.60,1:16:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜欢妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:16:12.52,1:16:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:16:16.13,1:16:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜欢妈妈吧
Dialogue: 0,1:16:19.88,1:16:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,1:16:23.18,1:16:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出来
Dialogue: 0,1:16:27.46,1:16:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜欢妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:16:29.85,1:16:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多说一些
Dialogue: 0,1:17:06.23,1:17:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:17:10.54,1:17:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好挺哦
Dialogue: 0,1:17:17.78,1:17:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆也很兴奋了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:23.32,1:17:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看妈妈的身体吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:26.63,1:17:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很兴奋吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:32.55,1:17:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多摸一些
Dialogue: 0,1:17:36.60,1:17:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让妈妈爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:17:43.48,1:17:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜欢妈妈的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:18:11.13,1:18:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:18:12.70,1:18:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样动好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:41.65,1:18:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴湿湿的吗
Dialogue: 0,1:18:57.01,1:19:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈好想舔小隆的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,1:19:02.07,1:19:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想舔哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:06.05,1:19:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想舔哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:09.16,1:19:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:11.41,1:19:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想哦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:35.18,1:19:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:30.44,1:20:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比小葵的口交更爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:21:16.05,1:21:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:21:28.15,1:21:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗 小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:21:31.53,1:21:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:21:45.70,1:21:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒真好吃
Dialogue: 0,1:21:51.31,1:21:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔小隆的肉棒 妈妈好幸福
Dialogue: 0,1:21:57.41,1:21:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:22.35,1:22:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吸 要射了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:27.88,1:22:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 要射了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:54.47,1:22:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆浓浓的精液
Dialogue: 0,1:23:01.46,1:23:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,1:23:04.00,1:23:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:23:05.62,1:23:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:23:08.30,1:23:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,1:23:14.60,1:23:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:23:17.09,1:23:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈也很喜欢小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:23:26.08,1:23:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 我们母子偏离了轨道 互相需求对方的身体
Dialogue: 0,1:23:35.42,1:23:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后
Dialogue: 0,1:23:51.67,1:23:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天
Dialogue: 0,1:23:54.75,1:23:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放学后
Dialogue: 0,1:23:58.36,1:24:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来我家玩吧
Dialogue: 0,1:24:07.89,1:24:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:24:37.42,1:24:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:24:39.02,1:24:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,1:24:42.56,1:24:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:24:44.00,1:24:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这边
Dialogue: 0,1:24:45.32,1:24:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也要吗
Dialogue: 0,1:24:47.45,1:24:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经做了一周了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:08.92,1:25:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也要做哦
Dialogue: 0,1:25:25.74,1:25:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点做吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:57.77,1:25:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:26:00.00,1:26:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你
Dialogue: 0,1:26:02.02,1:26:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,1:26:04.56,1:26:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你
Dialogue: 0,1:26:07.94,1:26:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:26:17.51,1:26:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:26:36.69,1:26:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看吧
Dialogue: 0,1:26:44.10,1:26:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,1:26:48.45,1:26:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:27:34.55,1:27:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:27:49.62,1:27:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:27:51.20,1:27:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:27:55.30,1:27:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,1:28:08.06,1:28:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我多舔一些
Dialogue: 0,1:28:58.74,1:29:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗 好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:29:08.77,1:29:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接摸吧
Dialogue: 0,1:29:12.26,1:29:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接摸了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:29:36.61,1:29:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗
Dialogue: 0,1:29:50.44,1:29:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽呢
Dialogue: 0,1:29:52.24,1:29:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:29:54.52,1:29:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴好爽呢
Dialogue: 0,1:30:02.26,1:30:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里
Dialogue: 0,1:30:07.72,1:30:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:30:10.85,1:30:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:30:50.01,1:30:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多做一些
Dialogue: 0,1:30:54.00,1:30:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,1:31:24.47,1:31:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽呢
Dialogue: 0,1:31:25.81,1:31:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看
Dialogue: 0,1:31:31.23,1:31:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地看吧
Dialogue: 0,1:31:39.26,1:31:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 看妈妈的骚穴
Dialogue: 0,1:31:46.28,1:31:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来摸吧
Dialogue: 0,1:31:53.24,1:31:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:31:57.19,1:31:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级湿的
Dialogue: 0,1:31:58.86,1:32:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:03.83,1:32:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更深。。。更深一些
Dialogue: 0,1:32:10.00,1:32:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:15.68,1:32:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害。。。好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:32:30.70,1:32:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更激励一些哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:40.08,1:32:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:43.52,1:32:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用手指让我高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,1:32:46.87,1:32:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骚穴好想要
Dialogue: 0,1:32:49.27,1:32:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:52.31,1:32:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:32:55.75,1:32:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多。。。更激励一点
Dialogue: 0,1:33:05.00,1:33:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:33:09.79,1:33:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:33:18.00,1:33:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗
Dialogue: 0,1:33:19.27,1:33:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:33:24.02,1:33:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的骚穴好吃吗
Dialogue: 0,1:33:49.05,1:33:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:33:50.25,1:33:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又去了
Dialogue: 0,1:34:05.00,1:34:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:34:06.52,1:34:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈来让你爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:34:32.84,1:34:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:34:39.44,1:34:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:34:50.51,1:34:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很好吃吧
Dialogue: 0,1:35:38.71,1:35:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:35:38.86,1:35:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里出了很多汗吧
Dialogue: 0,1:35:51.07,1:35:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好淫荡
Dialogue: 0,1:35:53.66,1:35:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很重的尿臭味呢
Dialogue: 0,1:35:58.00,1:36:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出了很多汗吧
Dialogue: 0,1:36:04.08,1:36:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,1:36:07.01,1:36:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翘起来了
Dialogue: 0,1:36:21.48,1:36:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈很喜欢尿的味道
Dialogue: 0,1:36:26.77,1:36:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,1:36:28.29,1:36:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:36:52.29,1:36:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好臭哦
Dialogue: 0,1:36:54.97,1:36:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好臭哦
Dialogue: 0,1:36:56.67,1:36:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好臭啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:02.46,1:37:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:37:05.11,1:37:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢这个味道
Dialogue: 0,1:37:10.84,1:37:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好兴奋啊
Dialogue: 0,1:37:37.82,1:37:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:38:14.59,1:38:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:38:38.90,1:38:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:39:06.33,1:39:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:39:23.32,1:39:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:39:30.69,1:39:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:40:00.69,1:40:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 屁股转过来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:40:24.61,1:40:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:40:57.71,1:40:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:40:58.73,1:41:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是只是妈妈舔 我也要舔
Dialogue: 0,1:41:06.20,1:41:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做吧
Dialogue: 0,1:41:12.90,1:41:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转过来
Dialogue: 0,1:41:18.74,1:41:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看
Dialogue: 0,1:41:34.64,1:41:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:41:34.87,1:41:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能舔屁眼
Dialogue: 0,1:41:39.32,1:41:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,1:41:54.62,1:41:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:41:57.28,1:41:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗  很爽
Dialogue: 0,1:42:04.31,1:42:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗  很爽 小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:42:20.48,1:42:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,1:42:23.06,1:42:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把肉棒插入妈妈的骚穴吧
Dialogue: 0,1:42:33.00,1:42:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手指还不够
Dialogue: 0,1:42:36.02,1:42:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以插入吗
Dialogue: 0,1:42:37.53,1:42:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快插入吧
Dialogue: 0,1:42:44.05,1:42:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里
Dialogue: 0,1:42:48.02,1:42:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扒开吧
Dialogue: 0,1:42:51.02,1:42:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到深处了吗
Dialogue: 0,1:42:55.70,1:42:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:42:56.97,1:42:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:42:58.73,1:43:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入吧
Dialogue: 0,1:43:04.00,1:43:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:43:10.56,1:43:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:43:24.21,1:43:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗 好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:43:30.28,1:43:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:43:40.30,1:43:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:43:44.55,1:43:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:43:47.02,1:43:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多
Dialogue: 0,1:43:56.36,1:43:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:01.00,1:44:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:44:03.57,1:44:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:07.25,1:44:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:44:08.53,1:44:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:44:10.86,1:44:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插得好深哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:14.65,1:44:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:29.29,1:44:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗
Dialogue: 0,1:44:30.62,1:44:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:44:37.27,1:44:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:44:41.69,1:44:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:45:08.06,1:45:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:45:10.79,1:45:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,1:45:14.46,1:45:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,1:45:23.02,1:45:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:45:26.21,1:45:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:45:40.66,1:45:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:45:42.02,1:45:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多插一些
Dialogue: 0,1:45:47.47,1:45:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这边
Dialogue: 0,1:45:55.82,1:45:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:46:00.00,1:46:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:46:07.48,1:46:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吗 超级爽
Dialogue: 0,1:46:11.07,1:46:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:46:13.04,1:46:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 好爽
Dialogue: 0,1:46:21.06,1:46:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:46:23.05,1:46:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起小葵 妈妈的骚穴更爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:46:29.55,1:46:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:46:37.37,1:46:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的肉棒最爽了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:00.62,1:47:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:47:19.09,1:47:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:47:26.71,1:47:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多做一些
Dialogue: 0,1:47:50.05,1:47:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:48:10.92,1:48:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:48:12.73,1:48:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我的腰好有力哦
Dialogue: 0,1:48:17.50,1:48:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:48:20.86,1:48:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天和平时不一样呢
Dialogue: 0,1:48:23.63,1:48:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:48:26.81,1:48:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈第一次这么爽
Dialogue: 0,1:48:30.31,1:48:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:48:37.31,1:48:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比平时更有力量呢
Dialogue: 0,1:48:54.78,1:48:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:49:05.42,1:49:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:49:15.95,1:49:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:49:21.16,1:49:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆 好好感觉吧
Dialogue: 0,1:49:25.25,1:49:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:49:27.67,1:49:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:49:36.67,1:49:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:49:48.65,1:49:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:49:57.12,1:49:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:50:11.15,1:50:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顶到子宫了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:50:17.29,1:50:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆很喜欢这里吧
Dialogue: 0,1:50:27.89,1:50:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:50:30.00,1:50:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,1:50:31.55,1:50:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然和妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:50:35.05,1:50:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵 你怎么来了
Dialogue: 0,1:50:37.57,1:50:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫她来的
Dialogue: 0,1:50:41.31,1:50:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊
Dialogue: 0,1:50:43.21,1:50:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈爱儿子的方式
Dialogue: 0,1:50:49.52,1:50:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:50:51.55,1:50:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆不需要女朋友
Dialogue: 0,1:50:56.54,1:51:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我在就够了
Dialogue: 0,1:51:01.03,1:51:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊
Dialogue: 0,1:51:03.05,1:51:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我做得这么爽呢
Dialogue: 0,1:51:16.47,1:51:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:51:18.09,1:51:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:51:40.17,1:51:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧 小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:51:48.84,1:51:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴比小葵的爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:52:13.30,1:52:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:52:25.89,1:52:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,1:52:29.28,1:52:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:52:30.48,1:52:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在小葵面前说吧
Dialogue: 0,1:52:33.46,1:52:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴更爽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:52:37.00,1:52:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的骚穴很爽
Dialogue: 0,1:53:12.32,1:53:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有感觉呢
Dialogue: 0,1:53:15.46,1:53:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有让小葵看过呢
Dialogue: 0,1:53:30.40,1:53:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:53:32.43,1:53:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和妈妈多做一些
Dialogue: 0,1:53:42.61,1:53:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入了哦
Dialogue: 0,1:53:51.41,1:53:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:53:55.02,1:53:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:54:08.35,1:54:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小葵
Dialogue: 0,1:54:10.66,1:54:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更近一些看吧
Dialogue: 0,1:54:26.51,1:54:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地看着小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:54:35.07,1:54:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,1:54:53.92,1:54:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:54:55.81,1:54:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,1:54:58.81,1:55:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了去了
Dialogue: 0,1:55:26.58,1:55:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈爽吗
Dialogue: 0,1:55:27.86,1:55:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽哦
Dialogue: 0,1:55:48.05,1:55:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:55:49.81,1:55:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射好的精液在妈妈的骚穴里吧
Dialogue: 0,1:55:56.34,1:55:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,1:55:58.21,1:55:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子的话会有孩子的
Dialogue: 0,1:56:00.98,1:56:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起养大吧
Dialogue: 0,1:56:07.39,1:56:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:56:09.20,1:56:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要你的精液
Dialogue: 0,1:56:12.86,1:56:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,1:56:14.89,1:56:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射在里面吧
Dialogue: 0,1:56:19.54,1:56:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级爽的
Dialogue: 0,1:56:23.39,1:56:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射好多精液出来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:56:27.00,1:56:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈要射了
Dialogue: 0,1:56:28.69,1:56:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:56:39.01,1:56:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,1:56:41.19,1:56:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好浓哦
Dialogue: 0,1:56:43.72,1:56:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆的精液
Dialogue: 0,1:56:46.46,1:56:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射进去了
Dialogue: 0,1:57:09.88,1:57:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小隆
Dialogue: 0,1:57:13.25,1:57:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈帮你舔干净哦
Dialogue: 0,1:57:22.05,1:57:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,1:57:24.13,1:57:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们太不对劲了
Dialogue: 0,1:57:59.92,1:58:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后小隆的女朋友再也没来过
Dialogue: 0,1:58:06.86,1:58:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子有我就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
