[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2018-03-14 22:35:59
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正兰亭超细黑简体,25,&H00250DB3,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000040,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,5,3,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.86,0:00:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在药剂公司上班
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也为了公司的新药\N前往医院推荐新药
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.97,0:00:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们公司的新药..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.02,0:00:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们公司的新药..
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.72,0:01:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于癌症的患者很有效
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.84,0:01:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这句话你已经说过了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.57,0:01:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道的是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.41,0:01:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的药和其他公司的药\N比起来有哪点比较好的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.75,0:01:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不说清楚一点\N我哪知道是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.68,0:01:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道的是这个好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.22,0:01:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的药厂的业务吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.19,0:01:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会拼命推销自己公司的药\N这点我懂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.56,0:01:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这个药的优缺点\N你却完全不跟我说明
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.40,0:01:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个根本就不行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.44,0:01:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公司好不容易开发的新药
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.40,0:01:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是业务却这样推销\N你这样有人会买吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.81,0:01:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让人伤脑筋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.06,0:02:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上迷你裙的女人\N美臀OL的访问羞耻营业
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.04,0:02:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样怎么行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.48,0:02:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚医院有打电话过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.35,0:02:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说你浪费了他一堆时间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.12,0:02:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.05,0:02:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经很努力向对方推销了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.39,0:02:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是就是没办法..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.49,0:02:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的..为什么\N你这种人也能当业务员
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.26,0:02:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.87,0:02:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.07,0:02:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只好拿出那招了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.81,0:04:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我穿上这个区跑业务吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.67,0:06:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前几天真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.41,0:06:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你很忙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.21,0:06:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请你再给我们一次机会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.26,0:07:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.03,0:07:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前几天真的很不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.70,0:07:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是川岛药剂公司的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.09,0:07:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站着说话也不方便
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.39,0:07:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来这边喝杯茶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.36,0:07:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这次的新药
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.13,0:07:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过我们确认这个药\N对癌细胞有很强的抑制作用
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.48,0:08:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此..那我们医院\N就进个两百箱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.39,0:08:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.17,0:08:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.47,0:08:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会穿这样来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.01,0:08:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代表你应该知道\N自己该做什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.41,0:08:35.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.38,0:08:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.25,0:08:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你住手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.86,0:08:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并没有那个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.39,0:08:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么要穿这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.20,0:08:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是为了挽回上次的失败
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.77,0:09:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才穿这么下流的裙子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.65,0:09:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.38,0:09:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.85,0:09:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.78,0:09:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的没有那个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.92,0:09:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很热吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.52,0:09:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.17,0:10:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把胸部露出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.19,0:10:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该也想要把
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.44,0:10:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好丰满的屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.63,0:11:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明就有那个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.34,0:11:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才穿成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.54,0:11:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正还有胸罩嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.27,0:11:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在这样也不能求救吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.77,0:12:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会有感觉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.57,0:12:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你说肉穴很舒服的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.44,0:12:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就再加买一百箱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.11,0:13:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的屁股真棒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.30,0:13:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上次穿那样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.77,0:13:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本没人会跟你买药的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.22,0:13:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股再往前一点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.70,0:13:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害的姿势
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.47,0:13:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有穿丝袜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.67,0:14:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是下流
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.50,0:15:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮时一定要叫出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.50,0:15:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把裙子掀起来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.28,0:15:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样很舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.24,0:15:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我摸看看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.41,0:15:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.78,0:15:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股再翘高一点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.77,0:16:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样如何啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.79,0:16:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉穴怎样了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.67,0:16:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把内裤脱掉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.92,0:17:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只要看肉穴而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.36,0:17:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股翘起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.81,0:17:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从内裤上摸就很舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.02,0:17:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接摸的话一定更舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.83,0:17:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你自己插进去的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.10,0:17:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你想要我插进去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.11,0:18:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插两根吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.98,0:18:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力扭你的屁股啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.74,0:19:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裙子都拉上去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.59,0:19:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个你要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.56,0:19:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害我变的这么硬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.53,0:19:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用嘴巴让我舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.31,0:19:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该知道该怎么做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.53,0:20:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看这种事你在别的地方\N也有做过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.14,0:20:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有做过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.91,0:20:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脚张开来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.91,0:20:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你也有那个意思吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.31,0:20:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,含到最里面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.54,0:21:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把裙子拉下去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.19,0:22:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一脸想要肉棒的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.16,0:22:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把屁股翘起来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.50,0:22:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚我不是教过你了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.42,0:23:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要我插进去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.93,0:23:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.27,0:23:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭着屁股求我把肉棒插进去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.05,0:23:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你插进来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.19,0:23:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我想要契约\N可是更想要肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.60,0:23:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我想要契约\N可是更想要肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.83,0:23:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你说的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.31,0:25:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢来
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.74,0:26:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.41,0:26:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把屁股朝这边
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.92,0:26:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.09,0:27:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么想要我买药吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.14,0:28:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裙子又上去了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.18,0:28:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.33,0:28:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插进去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.02,0:29:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让肉棒插进去
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.77,0:29:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好的动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.11,0:29:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.64,0:31:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把屁股翘起来
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.32,0:33:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只顾着自己爽
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.14,0:35:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 射到你的裙子上了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.02,0:35:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.19,0:35:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的药..我买了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.56,0:35:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.54,0:35:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是签到契约
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.04,0:35:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客户也很满意哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.78,0:35:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那就好..
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.06,0:36:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服用这个药之后
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.43,0:36:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会比之前的旧药更加有效
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.97,0:36:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是业务员对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.01,0:36:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没看到我现在正忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.88,0:36:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对起
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.82,0:36:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是拿你没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.63,0:36:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么不穿迷你裙过去
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.86,0:36:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.00,0:36:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.82,0:37:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.35,0:37:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你现在在忙
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.66,0:37:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以稍微借给我一点时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.37,0:37:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.31,0:37:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生 我可以跟你\N做一下说明吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.12,0:37:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.26,0:37:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是很忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.09,0:37:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本连休息时间都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.93,0:37:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在你开始说明之前
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.64,0:37:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以先让我发泄一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.55,0:38:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.98,0:38:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白你的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.39,0:38:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在穿成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.66,0:38:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该不是单纯来跑业务的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.23,0:38:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的没有那个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.13,0:38:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会我会听你说明的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.00,0:38:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生..
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.21,0:38:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又不是小孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.35,0:38:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生..
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.95,0:38:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实你是为了做这种事\N才来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.29,0:38:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.86,0:38:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁叫你要穿这种迷你裙
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.24,0:39:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你住手
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.54,0:39:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再让我看清楚一点嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.04,0:39:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是想看这个屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.31,0:40:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好暖和
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.16,0:41:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很湿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.95,0:42:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手指怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.67,0:42:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.41,0:42:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生
Dialogue: 0,0:45:41.01,0:45:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生..
Dialogue: 0,0:45:57.22,0:45:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我发泄一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:36.03,0:46:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿这样就是想诱惑我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:01.72,0:47:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的舌头舔我的鬼头
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.79,0:47:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看你的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.99,0:48:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得兴奋了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:50.16,0:48:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭你的腰
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.65,0:49:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生..
Dialogue: 0,0:51:52.71,0:51:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.13,0:52:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把屁股翘起来
Dialogue: 0,0:52:51.37,0:52:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:52:52.97,0:52:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然说出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.74,0:53:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插进来了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:33.00,1:00:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我射出来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:01.95,1:03:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部挤出来
Dialogue: 0,1:03:53.23,1:03:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从开始穿迷你裙以后
Dialogue: 0,1:03:55.73,1:03:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的业绩就不断的增长
Dialogue: 0,1:03:58.23,1:04:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到最后我连平时\N也开始穿迷你裙了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:07.04,1:04:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早
Dialogue: 0,1:06:37.76,1:06:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等！你要干什么
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.07,1:06:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁叫你要穿成这样来上班
Dialogue: 0,1:06:45.27,1:06:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你叫我穿的啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:48.30,1:06:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,1:06:55.01,1:06:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你住手
Dialogue: 0,1:06:59.88,1:07:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,1:07:03.05,1:07:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我乖乖的
Dialogue: 0,1:07:36.85,1:07:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要乱动
Dialogue: 0,1:07:51.03,1:07:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被人看到的啦
Dialogue: 0,1:07:56.71,1:07:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都出去了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:59.94,1:08:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好有人回来的
Dialogue: 0,1:08:48.39,1:08:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好香的味道
Dialogue: 0,1:08:52.26,1:08:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会很香
Dialogue: 0,1:08:57.97,1:09:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就喜欢这种味道
Dialogue: 0,1:09:22.06,1:09:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太棒了
Dialogue: 0,1:09:38.78,1:09:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好香
Dialogue: 0,1:12:50.27,1:12:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换我了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:16.99,1:19:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这全都是你不好
Dialogue: 0,1:22:31.15,1:22:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种药可以直接让患者服下
Dialogue: 0,1:23:32.64,1:23:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也有那个意思吧
Dialogue: 0,1:29:23.76,1:29:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是下流的内衣
Dialogue: 0,1:29:38.41,1:29:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然有这么棒的屁股
Dialogue: 0,1:31:43.93,1:31:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是下流的屁股
Dialogue: 0,1:33:01.38,1:33:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是下流的屁股
Dialogue: 0,1:33:53.56,1:33:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,1:33:57.23,1:33:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,1:34:35.24,1:34:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬上去
Dialogue: 0,1:36:43.53,1:36:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变的这么湿
Dialogue: 0,1:36:47.17,1:36:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里会发出很下流的味道哦
Dialogue: 0,1:37:40.32,1:37:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,1:40:38.80,1:40:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉穴变的这么湿
Dialogue: 0,1:40:43.67,1:40:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是好色
Dialogue: 0,1:42:43.66,1:42:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表情变的这么下流
Dialogue: 0,1:43:49.92,1:43:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舔的这么美味的样子
Dialogue: 0,1:43:57.73,1:44:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想要吧
Dialogue: 0,1:44:03.04,1:44:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很想要我插进去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:44:41.51,1:44:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒再摩擦你的胯下
Dialogue: 0,1:44:44.25,1:44:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你越来越想要了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:46:31.09,1:46:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁股再下来一点
Dialogue: 0,1:51:20.57,1:51:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要更激烈吗
Dialogue: 0,1:57:01.05,1:57:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会跟你签约的
Dialogue: 0,1:57:06.95,1:57:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,1:57:20.43,1:57:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我马上过去
Dialogue: 0,1:57:24.57,1:57:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我有穿
Dialogue: 0,1:57:39.82,1:57:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上迷你裙以后
Dialogue: 0,1:57:42.82,1:57:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管那家医院\N都会愿意和我签约
Dialogue: 0,1:57:45.13,1:57:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不知不觉中\N迷你裙已经变成我的制服了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
